[
  {
    "question": "Iveland",
    "answer": "Iveland"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lyngdal",
    "answer": "Lyngdal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Froland",
    "answer": "Froland"
  },
  {
    "question": "Evje og Hornnes",
    "answer": "Evje og Hornnes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Flekkefjord",
    "answer": "Flekkefjord"
  },
  {
    "question": "Kvinesdal",
    "answer": "Kvinesdal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Risør",
    "answer": "Risør"
  },
  {
    "question": "Kristiansand",
    "answer": "Kristiansand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Grimstad",
    "answer": "Grimstad"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lillesand",
    "answer": "Lillesand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Farsund",
    "answer": "Farsund"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tvedestrand",
    "answer": "Tvedestrand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bygland",
    "answer": "Bygland"
  },
  {
    "question": "Arendal",
    "answer": "Arendal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Åseral",
    "answer": "Åseral"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lindesnes",
    "answer": "Lindesnes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bykle",
    "answer": "Bykle"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sirdal",
    "answer": "Sirdal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Vennesla",
    "answer": "Vennesla"
  },
  {
    "question": "Åmli",
    "answer": "Åmli"
  },
  {
    "question": "Vegårshei",
    "answer": "Vegårshei"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hægebostad",
    "answer": "Hægebostad"
  },
  {
    "question": "Birkenes",
    "answer": "Birkenes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Valle",
    "answer": "Valle"
  },
  {
    "question": "Gjerstad",
    "answer": "Gjerstad"
  }
]